# SHEHROZ HUSSAIN

WEB DEVELOPER



# **3** 0301-3111022

✓ Mrshehrozhussain@gmail.com

Block 14 street 2 bag-e-umer Sargodha

#### PROFILE

I am a professional Web Developer with some experience, I really like the world of Web Designing & Web Development. I am an ambitious, diligent BSCS student with experience in computer applications and web development. I am searching for good career advancement possibilities where my talent and knowledge may be best applied and exploited for the benefit of the organization and myself.

### SKILLS

- Web Design
- Design Thinking
- Front End Coding
- Problem-Solving
- Computer Literacy
- Project Management Tools
- Strong Communication

#### **EXPERIENCE**

MAR 2022 - JUNE 2022 | SERV-TREE SOLUTIONS PVT. LTD.

#### INTERNEE DEVELOPER

- Working on the basics of HTML,CSS,Jquery and bootstrap
- Create designs for the company
- Experience in front-end technology
- Working on core PHP

#### JUNE 2022 - NOV 2022 | DYNATUNNERS

#### Junior Web Developer

- First 3 months i Work here as an internee
- Collaborated with other designers
- Managed complex projects from start to finish
- Translated requirements into polished, high-level designs
- Working on Wordpress
- Working on their HRIS system

## EDUCATION

2017 - 2021 | UNIVERSITY OF CENTRAL PUNJAB

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

2015 - 2017 | PUNJAB COLLEGE SARGODHA

Information and Computer Sciences